Guide to the Black Sport in Pittsburgh Oral History Collection ca.1980 AIS.1987.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographic Material, no date; II.
  - Prints, no date
    - Philadelphia Hilldale Baseball Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Indianapolis ABCs Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Cuban Giants Team Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Eagles Team Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia Stars Team Prints, Philadelphia Giants Team Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Dodgers Team Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Assortment of Negro League Player Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Assortment of Negro League Action and Game Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Assortment of Negro League East Meets West All Star Game Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Assortment of Negro League Team Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Forbes Field Stadium Prints, Yankee Stadium Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Major and Negro League Executive Personnel Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Jackie Robinson Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Joe Black Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Josh Gibson Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Satchel Paige Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Ernie Banks Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Oscar Charleston Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Lou Gehrig Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Walter Johnson, Grover Cleveland Alexander, Chief Bender, and Waite Hoyt Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Roy Dandridge, Willie Wells, Smokey Joe Williams, and Martin Dihigo Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Willie Mays Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Monte Irvin Prints Harold Tinker Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Harold Tinker Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Billie Holiday, Teenie Harris, and Erroll Garner Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Latin American Baseball Team and Player Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Early Pittsburgh Black Football Prints, Garfield Eagles Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Monticello Basketball Assocation Prints, Early Pittsburgh Basketball Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Bedford Dwellings Development Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Untitled Latin American Baseball Contact Sheets, no date (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - African American Segregation Prints, Civil Rights Protest Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Monticello Athletic Association Basketball, Pittsburgh Crawfords Contact sheets and Negatives, no date (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Untitled Rowing Print, no date (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Dominican Republic Baseball Prints, Negatives, no date (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Negative Strips, no date
    - Untitled Assortment of Carribean Baseball Negative Strips, no date (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Slides
    - Assortment of Caribbean Baseball Research Photos, no date (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Assortment of Early Pittsburgh African American Archival Photos; Hill District, Black Sport, no date (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Águilas Cibaeñas Dominican Professional Baseball Team Photos, no date (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - April 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cuba, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - April 1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - September 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - February 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - January 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - March 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - January 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - January 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - July 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - September 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - October 1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - February 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Dominican Republic, December 198 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Vera Clemente, Dominican Republic, December 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - March 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - April 1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Manuscripts, III.
  - Photo IDs and Permission Letters for Photo use and Research, no date (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Negro League Reunion, Three Rivers Stadium Newspaper Articles, September 12, 1988; September 14, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Printed Ephemera, IV.
  - Assortment of Negro League Related Ephemera, Baseball Ephemera, no date (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kings On The Hill Documentary VHS Sleeves, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Greenlee Field Layout Map, no date (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Black Sport in Pittsburgh Interview Cassettes, V.
  - Bailey, Cleveland (see Christian, Bus)
  - Barranti, Joe, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript; notes
  - Before the Babe, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes
  - Benswanger, Mrs. William (Eleanor), 1 cassette_tape 45 minutes - side 2 only
  - Brewer, Chet (see National Negro League)
  - Caye, Billy, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Christian, Bus; also contains interviews with Cleveland Bailey and Bill "Pigmeat" Robinson, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes
  - Clark, Clarence, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript; notes
  - Clark, Fred, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Crunkleton, John, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Dandridge, Ray (see National Negro League)
  - Dimperio, Pete, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Dorsey, Zerbie and James, Jr., 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Fixa, Hernando Rivera, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes
  - Goodman, Larnell, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes; transcript
  - Gordon, Gil, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Greenlee, Dr. Charles, 2 cassette_tapes 180 minutes
  - Harris, Bill, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes
  - Harris, Bill and Zuckerman, Ellie, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Harris, Teenie, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Hopkins, Jack, 2 cassette_tapes 150 minutes; transcript
  - Hughes, Charlie, 2 cassette_tapes 60 minutes-1 side recorded on each; transcript
  - Hughes, Walt, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes; transcript
  - Irwin, Ray, 3 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Jackson, Benny, 2 cassette_tape 120 minutes
  - Jackson, Helen, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Kemp, Ray, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Klausing, Chuck, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Koger, Ralph, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes; transcript
  - Kramer, Charles, 3 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Leonard, Buck (see National Negro League)
  - Mellix, Ralph, 5 cassette_tapes 300 minutes; transcript
  - Moody, Willis, 2 cassette_tapes 90 minutes; transcript
  - Napier, Ethumm, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - National Negro League Reunion, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes
  - Negro Leagues, 4 cassette_tapes 360 minutes
    Scope and Content Notes
    Four cassettes from a National Public Radio series was produced in 1980 and narrated by James Earl Jones. The NPR series was based on the book, Invisible Men: Life in Baseball's Negro Leagues by Donn Rogosin.
  - Nunn, Jr., Bill, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Page, Ted, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Parker Jack / Ware, Joe, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Patterson, Gabe, 3 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Phillips, Vernon, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes; transcript
  - Raddick, Nick, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Rainey, Walter, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes; transcript
  - Robinson, Jimmy Joe, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes; transcript
  - Rooney, Art, 2 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Rooney, James, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes
  - Solomon, Sam, 1 cassette_tape 60 minutes
  - Stewart, James, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes; transcript
  - Streeter, Sam, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes
  - Stuchicki, Joe, 1 cassette_tape 90 minutes
  - Tinker, Harold, 2 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Turner, Wyatt, 2 cassette_tapes 120 minutes
  - Utterback, Everett, 3 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Ware, Joe / Jack Parker, 2 cassette_tapes 180 minutes; transcript
  - Weiskirchner, Jay, transcript
  - Weiskircher, Russell, 3 cassette_tapes 225 minutes; transcript
  - Zuckerman, Ellie (see Bill Harris)